usanewsflash.com 2017-11-01

# Privacy Policy * USA Newsflash

[USA News Flash](http://www.usanewsflash.com/) – Privacy policy

The privacy of our visitors is very important to us and our intent is to preserve the Privacy by all means necessary.The information provided here will inform you on the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use (operate) and visit [USA News Flash](http://www.usanewsflash.com/), and how we safeguard that same information. You can rest assured that your personal information will never be leaked or sold to the third parties and that it is protected by us.

**Log Files.** As with other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AT&T or Comcast, ), the browser used by you to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer,Chrome,Firefox), your site visit time and the pages browsed by you throughout our site.

**Cookies and Web Beacons** We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include showing a popup during your visit, or the ability to login to some of our key features, such as forums.

We also visualize third party advertisements on [USA News Flash](http://www.usanewsflash.com/ "Healthy Food House") to support our site. Few of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site that also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser used by you to visit our site, and in some cases, whether or not you have installed Flash. Such application is generally applied for geotargeting purposes, e.g., (showing Chicago real estate ads to someone in Chicago) or showing certain ads, based on specific visited sites (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

**DoubleClick DART cookies** We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick service. The DART cookies may also be used by us for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). The cookie is used to serve your specific ads and your interests (“interest based targeting”). The ads served are to be targeted on the basis of your previous browsing history (For example, if you are viewing sites for visiting New York, you may also see New York hotels and places to visit, when viewing a non-related site, such as a hockey site). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”, which does NOT track your personal information, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You have the option to opt-out of this ad serving on all sites, using this advertising by visiting http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security, AVG, Avira, Kaspersky . However, it can affect your ability to interact with our site as well as other websites and it may include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless, you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

**COPYRIGHT**

Every single content and article on this website is copyrighted. If you want to use our content, contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
